Ke7gQMbIFLI|||Why are markets panicking over Trump's choice? Should we panic too?
4wCO1fdl9iU|||The psychology of riding a bubble that could burst at any moment
4cCGQFHrbK4|||The Second Palantir: Why You Can't Get 10x the Price Even If You Know It
BdNikaqw238|||A video to watch when you still don't know much about Ethereum
UVeJSmWGzRw|||3 Reasons to Buy IREN
zMHD_MYLZtU|||I made money investing, so why do I do YouTube? Questions from 100,000 subscribers
wLwygCnx7V8|||The coin market outlook of a person who was attracted to Bitcoin 5 years ago
ZM589mmdDcc|||1 Investment Metric That Will Distinguish a Bubble That Won't Burst (ft. Bitcoin, AI, Palantir)
iLUIU1sU1Ug|||Airen has tripled in 3 months, Rocket Lab has doubled. Are you really not selling it for 10 times?
4kJxnR-XIfY|||폭등하는 써클, 내 코인은 언제 오를까? 트럼프가 준 두번째 기회
Lszaj6NhNcA|||미장보다 국장? 대선 이후 현실이 될 3가지 변화들
LXzCL-duG14|||트럼프가 만들 새로운 버블, 제2의 팔란티어는?
-3odSn4Wi2E|||Trump's Dream of a Second Plaza Accord? Investors' Attitudes to the Great Transformation
iNAlXUEw9tc|||Ants' Struggle to Understand Trump's Whims
A2l1-lyzq4Q|||Announcement of winners of the publication event
q4vz1jhWS4s|||경제적 자유 이후의 현실... 그리고 특별한 이벤트
JzzXPN5v1BI|||양자컴퓨터 투자, 10년 전 비트코인과 같은 기회일까?
6Bk_eG77-5g|||How to study investment (important)
1xfjt7moZEg|||Stop Watching Bitcoin Halvings Anymore: How to Read Bitcoin Market Changes After Trump
AnHiiYa48Y0|||The final puzzle piece for an era where humans take orders from AI...
UVS-61j-76o|||Summary of Bitcoin Halving Concepts That We Missed 4 Years Ago
yxt087-C1zk|||Yonsei Value Investment Top Course | How to Create a Network for Asset Growth
QajNAfX5YvI|||Why I Quit YouTube After a Year, Even Though It Changed My Life
BQY0eh1lcUk|||30억 있는 30대 청년 300명이 모여 1조원을 모은다면?
79PFFmQQjOw|||Reasons for not buying NFTs
4bClsFvaoLs|||51% attack
RXdOkIaSIzc|||Changes in consumer habits after economic freedom
BeEHwOe-J98|||Palantir's Future Amidst the New Year's Market Crash
4UvO-6eecv8|||How to overcome investment failure and ride the wave of change | Introduction to World Studies Q&A
W0Jdfz35WE0|||Can Solana Kill Ethereum?
1bcmmTZRX5Q|||Memecoins and Meme Stocks, Are They Really Just a Game of Fate?
uMglUc_vQ6A|||Why Blockchain Popularization is Still in its Toddler Stage
EaclBpfxjCI|||넷플릭스 말고 틱톡처럼 살아야 하는 이유
0z8e_heKtKk|||Should we be concerned about Bitcoin crash after the Hungda bankruptcy and Tether collapse?
vpLSDLs6Fis|||Entrepreneurship is about financial freedom rather than a grand vision | Lee Han-byeol, CEO of Li...
cfwN1eWNlFA|||A 30-year-old YouTuber who made 30 years of money through investments
NlWaAL3SOxE|||빌게이츠가 투자한 푸드테크 비욘드미트를 알아보자
blAWrFLQ_Lc|||젊은 기부가 가성비 좋은 이유
qkpmS6yfO_g|||스팩(SPAC) 투자로 사업 확장하는 팔란티어
KvuATAaRxe8|||이더리움 소각 업데이트, 런던 하드포크를 알아보자
j3x7149DzDQ|||Characteristics of people who don't make progress no matter how hard they try
KkxAjOp-6H4|||Even if you want to get rich quickly, invest for the long term | Investment Theory, Episode 26
Y9JMqS87HEM|||Are you happy that you quit your job?
YkTfK92S8jA|||As the price of coins falls, the market matures.
sU0zaA0oJVk|||증시 나락 VS 초인플레이션 중에 고르기
bk-2Y0tjnZQ|||중국의 비트코인 채굴 금지, 비트코인 전력 낭비에 대한 생각
lFb4s3I5cKc|||엇갈리는 미래 전망, 아무도 믿지 마세요 | 투자학개론 25화
un9IHz9LnrA|||이더리움 뭐시기가 정말 대중화가 될까?
rde-ahZ29UQ|||A 30-year-old who quit his job to a job seeker
P-XpZ3l9DtQ|||Characteristics of People Who Lose Money Even When Prices Rise | Investment Theory, Episode 24
cjKV1A7UTvI|||We almost made 1 billion each, but we made 10 billion together | Investment Theory Episode 23
E0l6aYaff0U|||투자 공부는 어디서부터 시작해야 할까? | 투자학개론 22화
vE55S-x-6Lc|||YouTubers who don't want to increase their subscribers
CN_T1V1ocjg|||Wall Street Korean Fund Manager Who Lost All His Assets (Baidu Margin Call)
VdxXXSCbiEc|||두번째 닷컴 버블? 블록체인 물결의 주인공, 이더리움(ETH)을 알아보자
Qowcv46AneI|||퇴사한 직장인 유튜버가 말하는 인생 최고의 장기투자
Ol6u0WgN6E4|||가격 변동이 주는 착각에 대해 | 투자학개론 21화
aW0cZ-rmzz8|||Bubbles make rich people, whether they burst or rise | Investment Theory, Episode 20
NcijgSSeJVU|||30-year-old financial sector employee, resigning | Introduction to Retirement Studies
zRGNYWXHfV4|||지옥에서 돌아온 블랙베리를 알아보자
IOVmGeSwAMM|||30살 투자 유튜버가 20억 벌 때까지 자동차 안 산 이유 | 세상학개론학개론 QnA
Cgj6y_1_sS4|||The story of how I increased my assets 10-fold through investment during the Corona crisis (Portf...
oiAMDjdr334|||The 2021 Big Short? A Global Stock Market Crash Scenario Driven by the GameStop Butterfly Effect
Te7EzydvBT4|||A Fun Look at the GameStop (GME) Hedge Fund Short Squeeze
YbbV60KVe_c|||Palantir Demo Day Stock Surges 25%: What to Expect
u9okzlmKq_E|||팔란티어를 사게 된 3가지 이유
vR-IeyHBRkg|||비트코인 이더리움 10억원 넘게 있으면 안불안하신가요?
EYjyQFDTmfg|||비트코인 가격 변동이 여러분을 착각에 빠뜨립니다 | 투자학개론 19화
awxGkVGfQ_w|||Bitcoin 100 million?! A comfortable investment has a higher chance of success
4yZDpfDT7K8|||How Palantir, a nationalist company, is thriving under the Biden administration
4Bay6eXJH1Q|||Let's take a look at Palantir, a big data company with a nationalistic founder from PayPal.
UCX7_tJGgc4|||[언박싱]애플 투자자라면 모두 아이폰12를 삽시다
qXsMMse-vos|||Can you make 7x your investment in one year? | Investment Theory, Episode 18
5ZpG1gxdDfg|||Don't buy and sell based on price | Introduction to Investments, Episode 17
FrOAHoV0pH4|||My hobby is making my subscribers rich | Introduction to Investments Episode 16
3NUs0JElPvs|||I will answer the question of why you should not invest in Ripple.
QJf40N2wvh8|||The legendary secret to untie vinyl knots
zre4X1a4QlY|||2021 is the year of Bitcoin feat. Wall Street
vMmuwRuxpGA|||The legendary YouTuber who figured out the YouTube algorithm... | YouTube Studies 101
5I9wb6NKNUs|||How to get ahead in life | Introduction to Success
NVieilk8oHI|||교양있는 현대인을 위한 양주의 세계 | 음주학개론 4화
RNvKFfEru-o|||A realistic way to rise in status without marrying a conglomerate or making a fortune in business...
HK9jUm9lcEA|||How to Stay Mentally Unshakable During Stock Market Crashes | Investment Theory 8
5Py7WIb8iYw|||주식 폭락 필수 준비물 1위 | 투자학개론 6화
pmlsIYTKiw4|||How to Make Money Without Looking at a Graph | Investment 101, Episode 5
yWWdUIrVf34|||내가 20대에 5억원 모은 방법론 | 투자학개론 14화
OadsiFLklsM|||Warren Buffett Begins Investing in Gold for the First Time in 89 Years
qMhEf1864vc|||MicroStrategy - From Bitcoin Anti to Maxi in 7 Years
-JsPLE90h1Q|||How Diversification Destroys Returns | Introduction to Investment Studies, Episode 15
PPsCEEUIGqk|||재물운이 조금 더 좋아지는 방법 | 투자학개론 13화
tR5OyzvKCgE|||It's shabby, but I'll open the account as promised | Investment Theory Extra
MlFXn9P0YsM|||비트코인, 사기일까 미래일까?
4h-fPWoA2W4|||Is it a bubble if prices are skyrocketing? | Investment Theory 11
5aGn5CqbQls|||I regret the days when I didn't know about investing... | Introduction to Investment, Episode 3
ni_DydrX_uI|||Bitcoin, the secret to profit for millennial investors
AaJTT_GTkKY|||Why are stocks rising when the world is going to end? | Investment Theory 10
RrSo7nQFSGY|||Why the Economy and Stocks Are Going Against Each Other These Days | Investment Theory 9
XKisExNmEGc|||저축 10년 했는데 가난한 이유 | 투자학개론 2화
peYoNFd3z9E|||You can't get rich just by working comfortably | Introduction to Investment Studies, Part 1
J5_S29fQybw|||비트코인 어떻게 4년마다 30배가 오를까?
WVYVfmpLg4Q|||와인 디캔터  vs 위스키 디캔터 | 음주학개론 3화
eiC2ndorjDQ|||How to Catch the Bottom in a Stock Market Crash | Investment 101, Episode 7
Du_VW1HIG5s|||롤렉스 시계 라인업의 역사와 의미 알아보기 | 시계학개론
U3Xa3h3kztg|||술도 장비빨, 왠지 고독해보이는 음주 노하우 | 음주학개론 2화
7UoMvJPj0gw|||Things you need to know to pretend to drink wine | Introduction to Drinking Science, Part 1
O0OVrGY7JUc|||If you don't have this mindset, you won't make much money | Introduction to Investment, Episode 12
eXlKZ1D-mwM|||The most delicious way to burn money
7mzsY68IhhI|||The concept of living without working | Introduction to Investment Studies, Part 4
9cg-iVIkg20|||홍차 좀 마셔본 척 하려면 알아야 하는 것들 | 홍차학개론
JF34kovcvPk|||사진 좀 찍어본 척 하려면 알아야 하는 것들 | 사진학개론
ojsKQd_mJmk|||Things you need to know to pretend to wear perfume | Introduction to Perfume
